This girl, Kathy Geiger, got good grades
so we blindfolded her...
(Penny:)...tied her up
and left her in a cornfield overnight.
(Bernadette:)- God. That's awful.
- No, it was funny. Everyone laughed.
(Amy:)Did Kathy Geiger laugh?
(Penny:)Uh, probably. It's hard to say. She kind
of had an ear of corn in her mouth.
Who would've thought?
(Amy:)Fuzzy Fingers Fowler
is best friends with a bully.
- What?... I was not a bully.
- Kind of sounds like you were.
(Bernadette:)And maybe a felon.
(Amy:)Shh. That's how you
wind up in a cornfield.
(Raj:)Is that him over there?
(Leonard:)No.
(Raj:)How about that guy?
He looks like he'd hate you.
- I can really do this by myseIf.
- We're here to support you.
No, you're not. You're here to see if l
get my underwear pulled over my head.
(Howard:)You wore underwear?
Ha, ha. You fool.